paperkraft.blogspot.com 2009-12-30

# Paperkraft.net Privacy Policy | Paperkraft.net

##  [Paperkraft.net Privacy Policy](http://paperkraft.blogspot.com/2008/07/paperkraftnet-privacy-policy.html)

Posted by Ron | Tuesday, July 01, 2008 | [ 0 comments »](https://www.blogger.com/comment.g?blogID=22153773&postID=1292541228717664724)

Thank you for visiting Paperkraft.net (http://paperkraft.blogspot.com), a popular blog about anime, manga, video game, film and tv related papercrafts and paper models. At Paperkraft.net, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather.

LOG FILES AND USEAGE TRACKING

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited throughout our site.

COOKIES

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on Paperkraft.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your online security programs. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

YOUR CONSENTBy using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Paperkraft.net and third parties. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [Paperkraft.net](http://paperkraft.blogspot.com/)

Hat tip to [Jensense](http://www.jensense.com/2008/03/05/adsense-friendly-privacy-policy-sample-for-adsense-publishers-to-use/).
